Adedoyin A. Akintunde

Visual Designer - Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe XD, Canva And Figma

Email: Akintunde_afolabi@yahoo.com **Phone**: +2348133165161

Address: Ogun state, Nigeria Website: www.akintundeafolabi.wixsite.com/website

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/adedoyin-

akintunde-9a60901b4

I am a Visual Designer with Bsc in computer science, 4 years experience in graphics design and 1 year experience in product design(UI/UX design). At work i am focused on creating a minimalist design and also put attention to details, i also focus on creating responsive ui designs. I recently became fascinated with web development, so i am currently seeking to develop myself in this direction.

Work Experience

March 2022 - May 2022 Design Lea	larch 2022 - May 2022 Design Lead (Contract))
---	--	---

Stephen Akintayo Consulting

- -Designed all graphics content used for advert and publicity of the brand.
- -Designed responsive UI for the Brand websites.

March 2022 - May 2022 Graphics Designer (Contract)

Gtext Homes (gvest, gtext and associates, and gtext land)

- -Designed graphics content used for advert and publicity of the brand.
- -Colaborate with the design team and produce design content in respective to time required.

Feb 2022 - March 2022 Graphics Designer (Contract)

Corebank Nig.

- -Designed background images for the corebank website
- -Delivered high quality pngs for the website
- -Teamed up with the web developer to provide accredited designs

April 2021 - Feb 2022 Instructor (NYSC)

Nigerian Army School Of Electrical And Mechanical Engineering (NASEME)

- -Deliver lectures on Computer Management
- -Organized a graphic design class

Skills

Expert: Adobe Photoshop and Adobe illustrator

Advanced: Adobe XD and Figma

Familiar : Canva



Courses

	User Experience Design Essentials - Adobe XD UI UX Design (Udemy Adobe XD Mega Course - User Experience Design (92learns)	
Education		
2016 - 2022	Computer Science, Bachelor of Science	
	Kwara State University Malete, Kwara State	
Languages		
	Yoruba - Native speaker	
	English - Fluently	
Hobbies		
	Gaming(video games), sport(tennis, soccer and volleyball) , and watching anime	